在提供的示例代码里，你会注意到，
In the sample code provided you'll notice
我们创建了一个HTTP URL连接。
that we create a Http Url connection. To
为了使用Http协议在网络上发送和接收数据，
use Http to send and receive data over
Android里有两种客户端的API。
the network, we have two clients on Android.
一个是HttpUrlConnection类，还有一个是
The HttpUrlConnection class, as well as
Apache提供的HttpClient类。这两种方式都支持
the Apache HttpClient class. Both options support
Https，以数据流的形式上传和下载，超时配置，
Https, streaming uploads and downloads, configurable time outs,
IP v6以及连接池。
IP v6 and connection pooling. We recommend the
我们推荐使用HttpUrlConnection类，因为它更为通用，轻量级，
HttpUrlConnection class because it's general purpose and light
而且专门针对大多数Android应用的需求进行了优化。
weight, and it's been optimized to suit the needs of
想要了解更多的网络连接的知识，
most Android apps. To learn more about connecting to the
请参阅读下方的培训指南和博文链接。
network, see the training guide and blog post link below.